[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6801b5c75ab911699299b8fe"
  },
  "event": {
    "$oid": "680168ad16651446c257bb13"
  },
  "user": {
    "$oid": "68015c2be9d15da263edd48e"
  },
  "answers": [
    {
      "question": "How satisfied were you with the overall event?",
      "answer": "Yes",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b5c75ab911699299b8ff"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "Was the event content relevant to your interests?",
      "answer": "Good",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b5c75ab911699299b900"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "How effectively did the crux of the evnt was realised?",
      "answer": "Very Good",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b5c75ab911699299b901"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "Was the event organized and timely?",
      "answer": "Nice",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b5c75ab911699299b902"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "How would you rate the venue or online setup?",
      "answer": "Best",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b5c75ab911699299b903"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "What did you find most valuable in this event?",
      "answer": "Wow",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b5c75ab911699299b904"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "What could be improved for future events?",
      "answer": "Amazing",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b5c75ab911699299b905"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "Would you recommend this event to others?",
      "answer": "Awesome",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b5c75ab911699299b906"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "Did the event meet your expectations?",
      "answer": "Yes",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b5c75ab911699299b907"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "Any additional comments or feedback?",
      "answer": "No",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b5c75ab911699299b908"
      }
    }
  ],
  "createdAt": {
    "$date": "2025-04-18T02:15:35.706Z"
  },
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6801b6cc5ab911699299b953"
  },
  "event": {
    "$oid": "680168ad16651446c257bb13"
  },
  "user": {
    "$oid": "68015c2be9d15da263edd48e"
  },
  "answers": [
    {
      "question": "How satisfied were you with the overall event?",
      "answer": "Yes",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b6cc5ab911699299b954"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "Was the event content relevant to your interests?",
      "answer": "Liking It",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b6cc5ab911699299b955"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "How effectively did the crux of the evnt was realised?",
      "answer": "Yes",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b6cc5ab911699299b956"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "Was the event organized and timely?",
      "answer": "Sure",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b6cc5ab911699299b957"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "How would you rate the venue or online setup?",
      "answer": "Obviously",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b6cc5ab911699299b958"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "What did you find most valuable in this event?",
      "answer": "Experience is good",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b6cc5ab911699299b959"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "What could be improved for future events?",
      "answer": "A lot",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b6cc5ab911699299b95a"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "Would you recommend this event to others?",
      "answer": "Ok",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b6cc5ab911699299b95b"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "Did the event meet your expectations?",
      "answer": "Yes",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b6cc5ab911699299b95c"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "Any additional comments or feedback?",
      "answer": "--",
      "_id": {
        "$oid": "6801b6cc5ab911699299b95d"
      }
    }
  ],
  "createdAt": {
    "$date": "2025-04-18T02:19:56.305Z"
  },
  "__v": 0
}]